A Guide to the Recordings of the Virginia House of Delegates Sessions, 1981-2013
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Recordings of the Virginia House of Delegates Sessions, 1981-2013
The Library of Virginia
50627
23.55 cu. ft. (79 boxes)
Virginia. House of Delegates
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This accession was created 9 November 2012.
Accruals
This is an ongoing series, the Library of Virginia will continue to recieve the session recordings of the House of Delegates, future use-copies will continue to be added to accession 50627.
Custodial History
This is an artificial accession created for the use-copies of the recordings of the House of Delegates Sessions, preservation copies are filed under the accession numbers they were given upon reciept.
Biographical Information
The House of Delegates' predecessor, the House of Burgesses, was modeled after the House of Commons, in Parliament. The House of Burgesses existed from 1643 to 1776. The first session of the General Assembly, which took place in 1776, established the first constitution and made the House of Delegates the most powerful branch in state government. It was not until the constitution of 1851 was adopted that a more equitable balance among the branches of government was established. In the General Assembly, members of the House of Delegates and the Senate vote on legislation entered during the legislative session. Legislative bills can originate either in the House of Delegates or in the Senate, with both chambers having the ability to establish study committees. Each serves as a check upon the other to ensure a thorough debate on the merits of each bill. Currently the House of Delegates, together with the Senate, meets as the General Assembly in annual session, alternatively during thirty to sixty days. Currently there are 100 members of the House of Delegates, each representing a voting district in the Commonwealth.
Scope and Content
This collection contains the recorded sessions of the Virginia House of Delegates. These recordings document the proceedings of the House including inaugurations, opening prayers, committees, and house elections, as well as the debates surrounding house bills, senate bills and joint house resolutions. These recordings also allow you to see many of Virginia's key political figures as they rise through the ranks of state politics.
To find on what date an item was discussed consult the Journals of the House of Delegates of the Commonwealth of Virginia. (Call number J87 .V6 c; J87 .V7 c; J87 .V9 c .V7 .V9)
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Recordings
Contents List
- Series I. Recordings, 1981-2012., Extent: 23.55 cu. ft. (79 boxes). (Box 1-78)
  This collection is arranged chronologically by the first date listed. Some recordings cover multiple dates, and some dates span multiple discs or tapes.
  - 1982 (DVD)., .81 cu. ft. (3 boxes) (Box 1-4)
    - 1981-1982 - End - House. (Box 1)
    - 1982 Jan 13-16, 18 - House and Governor's Speech (3 discs). (Box 1)
    - 1982 Jan 19-22 - House Master. (Box 1)
    - 1982 Jan 19, 21, 28; Feb 2, 4 - General Laws (3 discs). (Box 1)
    - 1982 Jan 20 - Privileges and Elections. (Box 1)
    - 1982 Jan 25-28 - (2 discs). (Box 1)
    - 1982 Jan 28-29; Feb 5, 8 - House (3 discs). (Box 1)
    - 1982 Feb 1-4 - House (2 discs). (Box 1)
    - 1982 Feb 4, 9, 11 - General Laws (2 discs). (Box 1)
    - 1982 Feb 9-11 - House (3 discs). (Box 1)
    - 1982 Feb 12 - General Laws (3 discs). (Box 1)
    - 1982 Feb 12, 15 - House (3 discs). (Box 1)
    - 1982 Feb 12-16, 22-24 - Courts of Justice (2 discs). (Box 1)
    - 1982 Feb 14 - Finance (3 discs). (Box 1, 2)
    - 1982 Feb 15-16, 19 - Finance (3 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 15-16 - Health and Welfare (3 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 16 - House (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 16, 23; Mar 4 - Health and Welfare. (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 17 - House Master (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 17-18 - House Master (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 18 - House Master (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 18-19 - House Master (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 19 - House Master (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 19-20 - House Log, H.B. 177-777 (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 20 - House Log, HB 461, HB 441, HB 438 ( 2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 20 - House Log, HJR p.23-45, SJR 23, HLR 16, HB 795, HJR 78 (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 20, 22 - House Log (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 23-25 - Budget Bill (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 23, 25 - General Laws (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 23-25; Mar 2-4 - Health and Welfare (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 24 - Privileges and Elections (2 discs). (Box 2)
    - 1982 Feb 24-25; Mar 1 - Finance (2 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Feb 25-26 - House (2 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 1 - House Master (2 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 1-2 - Gas Tax (2 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 1, 3 - Finance (2 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 2-3 - House (2 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 2, 4 - General Laws (3 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 2, 4, 9 - Corp., Insur., Banking (2 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 4-5 - House Master (2 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 4, 9 - General Laws. (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 8-9 - House Master (3 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 8, 11 - Finance. (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 10 - House (3 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 10-11 - House (3 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 12 - House (3 discs). (Box 3)
    - 1982 Mar 12-13 - House (3 discs). (Box 4)
    - 1982 Mar 13 - House (3 discs). (Box 4)
    - 1982 Mar 13; Apr 1 - House (3 discs). (Box 4)
    - 1982 Apr 21 - House (2 discs). (Box 4)
  - 1983 (DVD)., 1.6 cu. ft. (6 boxes) (Box 4-11)
    - 1983 Jan 12 - Opening. (Box 4)
    - 1983 Jan 12 - Governor's Speech. (Box 4)
    - 1983 Jan 12-19 (3 discs). (Box 4)
    - 1983 Jan 13. (Box 4)
    - 1983 Jan 14, 17-19. (Box 4)
    - 1983 Jan 17 - Finance (3 discs). (Box 4)
    - 1983 Jan 17, 19, 24, 26 - General Laws (3 discs). (Box 4)
    - 1983 Jan 18. (Box 4)
    - 1983 Jan 18, 25, 27; feb 1 - CIB (3 discs). (Box 4)
    - 1983 Jan 19, 20, 24, 31 - Finance (3 discs). (Box 5)
    - 1983 Jan 19, 26; Feb 2 - Privileges and Elections (2 disks). (Box 5)
    - 1983 Jan 20. (Box 5)
    - 1983 Jan 20 - Finance (2 discs). (Box 5)
    - 1983 Jan 20, 21, 24-27 - (2 disks). (Box 5)
    - 1983 Jan 21. (Box 5)
    - 1983 Jan 25, 27 - Courts of Justice. (Box 2)
    - 1983 Jan 26. (Box 5)
    - 1983 Jan 27. (Box 5)
    - 1983 Jan 27; Feb 1 - Courts of Justice (3 discs). (Box 5)
    - 1983 Jan 28 - (6 discs). (Box 5)
    - 1983 Jan 29, 31; Feb 1, 2 - (3 discs). (Box 5, 6)
    - 1983 Jan 29. (Box 6)
    - 1983 Jan 29, 31. (Box 6)
    - 1983 Jan 31. (Box 6)
    - 1983 Jan 31; Feb 2 - General Laws (3 discs). (Box 6)
    - 1983 Jan 31; Feb 2, 4 - Finance (3 discs). (Box 6)
    - 1983 Feb 1 - (2 discs). (Box 6)
    - 1983 Feb 2. (Box 6)
    - 1983 Feb 2, 3. (Box 6)
    - 1983 Feb 2-3 - (2 discs). (Box 6)
    - 1983 Feb 3. (Box 6)
    - 1983 Feb 3 - Privileges and Elections. (Box 6)
    - 1983 Feb 3, 4 - CIB (3 discs). (Box 6)
    - 1983 Feb 4 - (2 discs). (Box 6)
    - 1983 Feb 4, 14 - Finance (3 discs). (Box 6, 7)
    - 1983 Feb 4, 16, 22 - Privileges and Elections (2 discs). (Box 7)
    - 1983 Feb 5, 15, 17 - CIB - Part 2 (3 discs). (Box 7)
    - 1983 Feb 6 - (2 discs). (Box 7)
    - 1983 Feb 6 - (3 discs). (Box 7)
    - 1983 Feb 7 - (6 discs). (Box 7)
    - 1983 Feb 7 - (11 discs). (Box 7, 8)
    - 1983 Feb 7, 8. (Box 8)
    - 1983 Feb 7, 8 - (3 discs). (Box 8)
    - 1983 Feb 8 - (7 discs). (Box 8)
    - 1983 Feb 8, 9 - (3 discs). (Box 8)
    - 1983 Feb 9. (Box 8)
    - 1983 Feb 9, 14 - General Laws. (Box 8)
    - 1983 Feb 10. (Box 8)
    - 1983 Feb 10, 11, 14, 15, 22 - (3 discs). (Box 8)
    - 1983 Feb 10-12, 15, 22 - Courts of Justice (3 discs). (Box 9)
    - 1983 Feb 11. (Box 9)
    - 1983 Feb 14 - (2 discs). (Box 9)
    - 1983 Feb 14, 16, 22 - Finance (3 discs). (Box 9)
    - 1983 Feb 15 - (2 discs). (Box 9)
    - 1983 Feb 16. (Box 9)
    - 1983 Feb 16-17, 18 - (3 discs). (Box 9)
    - 1983 Feb 16, 22 - General Laws and Courts of Justice (3 discs). (Box 9)
    - 1983 Feb 17 - (2 discs). (Box 9)
    - 1983 Feb 18 - (2 discs). (Box 9)
    - 1983 Feb 18, 21, 22 - (3 discs). (Box 9)
    - 1983 Feb 21 - (3 discs). (Box 10)
    - 1983 Feb 22 - (3 discs). (Box 10)
    - 1983 Feb 22, 23, 24 - (3 discs). (Box 10)
    - 1983 Feb 23 - (3 discs). (Box 10)
    - 1983 Feb 24 - (3 discs). (Box 10)
    - 1983 Feb 24 - (7 discs). (Box 10)
    - 1983 Feb 25 - (5 discs). (Box 11)
    - 1983 Feb 25, 26. (Box 11)
    - 1983 Feb 25-26 - (3 discs). (Box 11)
    - 1983 Feb 26, 27 - (3 discs). (Box 11)
    - 1983 Feb 27 - (3 discs). (Box 11)
    - 1983 Apr 16 - Reconvened. (Box 11)
    - 1983 - Last Day(2 discs). (Box 11)
  - 1984 (DVD)., 2.7 cu, ft. (10 boxes) (Box 11-21)
    - 1984 Jan 11 - House Opening Session (2 discs). (Box 11)
    - 1984 Jan 11 - (2 discs). (Box 11)
    - 1984 Jan 12, 13, 16. (Box 11)
    - 1984 Jan 12-13, 16-19 - (2 discs). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 16 - Finance. (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 16, 17 - General Laws (Time 60:00). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 16, 18, 23 - General Laws (2 discs). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 16, 23 - Finance (2 discs). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 17 - House, CIB, Courts of Justice (46:44). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 17, 19, 20, 24 - Courts of Justice (2 discs). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 17, 19, 24, 31 - CIB (2 discs). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 18, 25; Feb 1, 8 - Privileges and Elections (2 discs). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 19. (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 19 - Courts of Justice (56:56). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 20 - Courts of Justice (57:55). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 20, 23-25 - (2 discs). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 23 - General Assembly and Laws. (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 23 - General Assembly and Finance. (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 23 - Finance. (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 24. (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 24-25 - General Assembly (35:00). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 24, 26 - Courts of Justice (2 discs). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 25 - Finance (2 discs). (Box 12)
    - 1984 Jan 25 - General Laws (2 discs). (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 25, 31 - General Laws (2 discs). (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 26 - Calendar, Bills Referred. (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 26. (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 26 - General Assembly; Courts of Justice (50:47). (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 26-27, 30 (2 discs). (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 27 - Calendar, Bill Referred. (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 27. (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 27, 31 - Courts of Justice. (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 30 (3 discs). (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 30, 31 (2 discs). (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 31 - Finance (3 discs). (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 31 - Courts of Justice (5 discs). (Box 13)
    - 1984 Jan 31 - Calendar, Bill Referred (2 discs). (Box 13, 14)
    - 1984 Feb 1 - General Laws (2 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 1 - Finance (2 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 1, 2 (2 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 1, 6 - Finance (2 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 2 - Calendar, Bill Referred (4 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 2, 3 - Courts of Justice (2 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 1, 3, 6 (2 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 2, 7 - CIB (2 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 3 - Calendar, Bill Referred. (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 3, 7 - Courts of Justice (2 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 6 - Calendar, Bill Referred (3 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 6-7, 8 (2 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 6, 8 - General Laws (2 discs). (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 7, 8 - Calendar, Bill Referred. (Box 14)
    - 1984 Feb 7, 9 - Courts of Justice(2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 8 - Calendar, Bills Referred (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 8 - Finance (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 8, 9 (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 8, 10 - Finance. (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 8, 13, 22 - Privileges and Elections (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 9 - Calendar, Bills Referred (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 9 - Rules, Courts of Justice (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 9, 10 (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 9, 10 - CIB (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 9, 10 - Courts of Justice (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 10 - Calendar, Bills Referred (3 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 10-11 (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 10, 11 - CIB (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 10, 11 - Courts of Justice (2 discs). (Box 15)
    - 1984 Feb 10, 20, 27 - Finance (2 discs). (Box 16)
    - 1984 Feb 11 - General Laws. (Box 16)
    - 1984 Feb 11 - Calendar, Bills Referred (3 discs). (Box 16)
    - 1984 Feb 11 - CIB (2 discs). (Box 16)
    - 1984 Feb 11 - Courts of Justice (3 discs). (Box 16)
    - 1984 Feb 11, 12 (2 discs). (Box 16)
    - 1984 Feb 11, 16, 21 - CIB (2 discs). (Box 16)
    - 1984 Feb 12 - Calendar, Bills Referred (2 discs). (Box 16)
    - 1984 Feb 12, 13 (2 discs). (Box 16)
    - 1984 Feb 12, 15 - Courts of Justice (2 discs). (Box 16)
    - 1984 Feb 13 - Calendar, Bills Referred (6 discs). (Box 16)
    - 1984 Feb 13, 14 (3 discs). (Box 17)
    - 1984 Feb 14 - Calendar, Bills Referred (8 discs). (Box 17)
    - 1984 Feb 14 (3 discs). (Box 17)
    - 1984 Feb 14, 15-16, 20 (3 discs). (Box 17)
    - 1984 Feb 15-17 - Calendar, Bills Referred. (Box 17)
    - 1984 Feb 15, 20, 22 - General Laws (2 discs). (Box 17)
    - 1984 Feb 16, 17, 21, 23 - Courts of Justice (3 discs). (Box 17)
    - 1984 Feb 20 - Calendar, Bills Referred (2 discs). (Box 17)
    - 1984 Feb 20, 21, 22 (3 discs). (Box 18)
    - 1984 Feb 21 - Calendar, Bills Referred (2 discs). (Box 18)
    - 1984 Feb 21, 23, 26; Mar 5 - CIB, Finance. (Box 18)
    - 1984 Feb 22 - Calendar, Bills Referred (2 discs). (Box 18)
    - 1984 Feb 22, 23-24, 27 (3 discs). (Box 18)
    - 1984 Feb 22, 27, 29 - General Laws, Privileges and Elections (3 discs). (Box 18)
    - 1984 Feb 23 - Calendar, Bills Referred (2 discs). (Box 18)
    - 1984 Feb 23, 24, 28; Mar 1 - Courts of Justice (3 discs). (Box 18)
    - 1984 Feb 24 - General Assembly (Time 40:00). (Box 18)
    - 1984 Feb 24 - Calendar, Bills Referred (2 discs). (Box 18)
    - 1984 Feb 27 - Calendar, Bills Referred (3 discs). (Box 18, 19)
    - 1984 Feb 27, 28 (3 discs). (Box 19)
    - 1984 Feb 27, 29; Mar 5 - Finance (3 discs). (Box 19)
    - 1984 Feb 28 - Calendar, Bills Referred (3 discs). (Box 19)
    - 1984 Feb 29 - Calendar, Bills Referred. (Box 19)
    - 1984 Feb 29; Mar 1-2, 5 (3 discs). (Box 19)
    - 1984 Mar 1, 2, 6 - Courts of Justice (3 discs). (Box 19)
    - 1984 Mar 2 - Calendar, Bills Referred (Time 59:55). (Box 19)
    - 1984 Mar 5 - Calendar, Bills Referred (4 discs). (Box 19)
    - 1984 Mar 5, 6 (3 discs). (Box 19)
    - 1984 Mar 6 - Calendar, Bills Referred (4 discs). (Box 20)
    - 1984 Mar 6, 7-8 (3 discs). (Box 20)
    - 1984 Mar 7 (2 discs). (Box 20)
    - 1984 Mar 7 - Calendar, Bills Referred (2 discs). (Box 20)
    - 1984 Mar 8 - Calendar, Bills Referred (3 discs). (Box 20)
    - 1984 Mar 9 - Calendar, Bills Referred (6 discs). (Box 20)
    - 1984 Mar 9, 10 (3 discs). (Box 20)
    - 1984 Mar 10 - Calendar, Bills Referred (4 discs). (Box 21)
    - 1984 Mar 11 - Calendar, Bills Referred. (Box 21)
    - 1984 Mar 11-12; Apr 18 (2 discs). (Box 21)
    - 1984 Apr 18 - Calendar, Bills Referred. (Box 21)
    - 1984 Dec 17 - Special Session. (Box 21)
    - 1984. (Box 21)
  - 1985 (DVD)., .81 cu. ft. (3 boxes) (Box 21-23)
    - 1985 Jan 9-11, 14-16. (Box 21)
    - 1985 Jan 17-18, 21 (3 discs). (Box 21)
    - 1985 Jan 21-22 (2 discs). (Box 21)
    - 1985 Jan 22. (Box 21)
    - 1985 Jan 23-25 (3 discs). (Box 21)
    - 1985 Jan 23-25 (3 discs). (Box 21)
    - 1985 Jan 25-28. (Box 22)
    - 1985 Jan 25, 28-29 (2 discs). (Box 22)
    - 1985 Jan 30 (2 discs). (Box 22)
    - 1985 Jan 31; Feb 1 (3 discs). (Box 22)
    - 1985 Feb 1, 2 (3 discs). (Box 22)
    - 1985 Feb 2, 3 (3 discs). (Box 22)
    - 1985 Feb 3 (6 discs). (Box 22)
    - 1985 Feb 4 (3 discs). (Box 22)
    - 1985 Feb 4, 5-6 (3 discs). (Box 22)
    - 1985 Feb 7-8, 11-12 (3 discs). (Box 22)
    - 1985 Feb 13-14 (3 discs). (Box 22)
    - 1985 Feb 15-18 (3 discs). (Box 23)
    - 1985 Feb 19, 20 (3 discs). (Box 23)
    - 1985 Feb 20-21 (3 discs). (Box 23)
    - 1985 Feb 22, 23 (3 discs). (Box 23)
    - 1985 Feb 23 (2 discs). (Box 23)
    - 1985 Apr 3 (3 discs). (Box 23)
  - 1986 (DVD)., .54 cu. ft. (2 boxes) (Box 23-25)
    - 1986 Jan 8-10, 13 (2 discs). (Box 23)
    - 1986 Jan 14-21 (2 discs). (Box 23)
    - 1986 Jan 22-24, 27-28 (2 discs). (Box 23)
    - 1986 Jan 29-30 (3 discs). (Box 23)
    - 1986 Jan 31; Feb 3 (3 discs). (Box 23)
    - 1986 Feb 3, 4-5, 6 (3 discs). (Box 23)
    - 1986 Feb 6, 7 (3 discs). (Box 24)
    - 1986 Feb 7, 8 (3 discs). (Box 24)
    - 1986 Feb 8, 9 (3 discs). (Box 24)
    - 1986 Feb 9, 10 (3 discs). (Box 24)
    - 1986 Feb 10 (3 discs). (Box 24)
    - 1986 Feb 11 (3 discs). (Box 24)
    - 1986 Feb 12-14, 17-18, 19 (3 discs). (Box 24)
    - 1986 Feb 19, 20, 21 (3 discs). (Box 24)
    - 1986 Feb 21, 24, 25 (3 discs). (Box 24)
    - 1986 Feb 25, 26, 27 (3 discs). (Box 24)
    - 1986 Feb 27, 28 (3 discs). (Box 24, 25)
    - 1986 Mar 3, 4 (3 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 Mar 4, 5-6 (3 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 Mar 7, 8 (3 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 Mar 8 (2 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 Apr 16 - Veto Session (2 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 Sept 15-17 - Special Session (2 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 Sept 18, 22 - Special Session(2 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 Sept 22 - Special Session (2 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 Sept 22, 23-24 - Special Session (2 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 Sept 25 - Special Session (2 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 Sept 28 - Special Session (2 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 - No. 2 (3 discs). (Box 25)
    - 1986 - No. 7 (4 discs). (Box 25)
  - 1987 (DVD)., 1 cu. ft. (4 boxes) (Box 25-28)
    - 1987 Jan 14. (Box 25)
    - 1987 Jan 14, 15, 16, 19, 20, 21. (Box 25)
    - 1987 Jan 15. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 16. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 19. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 20. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 21. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 22. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 22, 23, 26, 27. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 23. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 26. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 27 (3 discs). (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 28. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 29. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Jan 30. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Feb 2 (2 discs). (Box 26)
    - 1987 Feb 3 (2 discs). (Box 26)
    - 1987 Feb 4. (Box 26)
    - 1987 Feb 5 (2 discs). (Box 26)
    - 1987 Feb 6 (2 discs). (Box 26)
    - 1987 Feb 7 (4 discs). (Box 26, 27)
    - 1987 Feb 8 (7 discs). (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 9 (3 discs). (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 10. (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 11. (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 12. (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 13. (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 16. (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 17. (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 18. (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 19. (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 20. (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 23 (2 discs). (Box 27)
    - 1987 Feb 23, 24 (4 discs). (Box 27, 28)
    - 1987 Feb 24 (3 discs). (Box 28)
    - 1987 Feb 25 (4 discs). (Box 28)
    - 1987 Feb 26 (3 discs). (Box 28)
    - 1987 Feb 27 (2 discs). (Box 28)
    - 1987 Feb 27, 28 (3 discs). (Box 28)
    - 1987 Feb 28 (2 discs). (Box 28)
    - 1987 - Reconvened Session, Veto (2 discs). (Box 28)
    - 1987 - Special Session. (Box 28)
  - 1988 (DVD)., 1 cu. ft. (4 boxes) (Box 28-31)
    - 1988 Jan 13 (2 discs). (Box 28)
    - 1988 Jan 14. (Box 28)
    - 1988 Jan 15. (Box 28)
    - 1988 Jan 18. (Box 28)
    - 1988 Jan 19. (Box 28)
    - 1988 Jan 20. (Box 29)
    - 1988 Jan 21. (Box 29)
    - 1988 Jan 22. (Box 29)
    - 1988 Jan 25. (Box 29)
    - 1988 Jan 26. (Box 29)
    - 1988 Jan 27. (Box 29)
    - 1988 Jan 28. (Box 29)
    - 1988 Jan 29. (Box 29)
    - 1988 Feb 1 (2 discs). (Box 29)
    - 1988 Feb 2 (2 discs). (Box 29)
    - 1988 Feb 3. (Box 29)
    - 1988 Feb 4 (2 discs). (Box 29)
    - 1988 Feb 5. (Box 29)
    - 1988 Feb 8 (2 discs). (Box 29)
    - 1988 Feb 9 (2 discs). (Box 29)
    - 1988 Feb 10 (2 discs). (Box 29)
    - 1988 Feb 11 (2 discs). (Box 29)
    - 1988 Feb 12 (2 discs). (Box 29)
    - 1988 Feb 13 (4 discs). (Box 29, 30)
    - 1988 Feb 14 (2 discs). (Box 30)
    - 1988 Feb 15 (5 discs). (Box 30)
    - 1988 Feb 16 (3 discs). (Box 30)
    - 1988 Feb 17. (Box 30)
    - 1988 Feb 18. (Box 30)
    - 1988 Feb 19. (Box 30)
    - 1988 Feb 22. (Box 30)
    - 1988 Feb 23. (Box 30)
    - 1988 Feb 24 (2 discs). (Box 30)
    - 1988 Feb 25. (Box 30)
    - 1988 Feb 26. (Box 30)
    - 1988 Feb 29. (Box 30)
    - 1988 Mar 1 (2 discs). (Box 30)
    - 1988 Mar 2 (2 discs). (Box 30)
    - 1988 Mar 3. (Box 30)
    - 1988 Mar 4. (Box 30)
    - 1988 Mar 7 (2 discs). (Box 31)
    - 1988 Mar 8 (2 discs). (Box 31)
    - 1988 Mar 9. (Box 31)
    - 1988 Mar 10 (3 discs). (Box 31)
    - 1988 Mar 11 (2 discs). (Box 31)
    - 1988 Mar 12 (4 discs). (Box 31)
    - 1988 Apr 20. (Box 31)
  - 1989 (DVD)., 1 cu. ft. (4 boxes) (Box 31-34)
    - 1989 Jan 11 (2 discs). (Box 31)
    - 1989 Jan 12. (Box 31)
    - 1989 Jan 13. (Box 31)
    - 1989 Jan 16. (Box 31)
    - 1989 Jan 17. (Box 31)
    - 1989 Jan 18. (Box 31)
    - 1989 Jan 19. (Box 31)
    - 1989 Jan 20. (Box 31)
    - 1989 Jan 23. (Box 31)
    - 1989 Jan 24 (2 discs). (Box 31)
    - 1989 Jan 25. (Box 32)
    - 1989 Jan 26. (Box 32)
    - 1989 Jan 27. (Box 32)
    - 1989 Jan 30. (Box 32)
    - 1989 Jan 31 (2 discs). (Box 32)
    - 1989 Feb 1. (Box 32)
    - 1989 Feb 2 (2 discs). (Box 32)
    - 1989 Feb 3 (2 discs). (Box 32)
    - 1989 Feb 4 (5 discs). (Box 32)
    - 1989 Feb 5 (2 discs). (Box 32)
    - 1989 Feb 6 (6 discs). (Box 32)
    - 1989 Feb 7 (3 discs). (Box 32)
    - 1989 Feb 8 (2 discs). (Box 32)
    - 1989 Feb 9. (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 10. (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 13. (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 14. (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 15. (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 16. (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 17. (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 20 (2 discs). (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 21 (3 discs). (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 22 (3 discs). (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 23 (4 discs). (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 24 (2 discs). (Box 33)
    - 1989 Feb 25 (4 discs). (Box 33)
    - 1989 Apr 5 - Reconvened Session. (Box 33)
    - 1989 Apr 24 - Special Session. (Box 33)
    - 1989 Apr 25 - Special Session. (Box 34)
    - 1989 Apr 26 - Special Session (3 discs). (Box 34)
    - 1989 Apr 27 - Special Session (3 discs). (Box 34)
    - 1989 June 7 - Reconvened Session II. (Box 34)
  - 1990 (DVD)., 1 cu. ft. (4 boxes) (Box 34-37)
    - 1990 Jan 10, 11, 12. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Jan 12. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Jan 12, 13. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Jan 15-17. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Jan 18-19, 22. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Jan 22, 23. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Jan 25. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Jan 26, 29. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Jan 29, 30-31. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Feb 1. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Feb 2. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Feb 5. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Feb 5, 6. (Box 34)
    - 1990 Feb 6, 7. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 7. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 8. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 8, 9. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 10. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 10, 11. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 11 (4 discs). (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 12, 13. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 13 (4 discs). (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 14-16. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 19, 20. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 20. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 21 - Budget. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 21, 22 - Budget. (Box 35)
    - 1990 Feb 23. (Box 36)
    - 1990 Feb 26 (2 discs). (Box 36)
    - 1990 Feb 26, 27. (Box 36)
    - 1990 Feb 27. (Box 36)
    - 1990 Feb 28. (Box 36)
    - 1990 Mar 1. (Box 36)
    - 1990 Mar 1, 2. (Box 36)
    - 1990 Mar 2. (Box 36)
    - 1990 Mar 5. (Box 36)
    - 1990 Mar 6 (2 discs). (Box 36)
    - 1990 Mar 6, 7. (Box 36)
    - 1990 Mar 7 (3 discs). (Box 36)
    - 1990 Mar 8 (3 discs). (Box 36)
    - 1990 Mar 8, 9. (Box 36)
    - 1990 Mar 9, 10. (Box 37)
    - 1990 Mar 10 (3 discs). (Box 37)
    - 1990 Apr 18 (2 discs). (Box 37)
    - 1991 Jan 9 (2 discs). (Box 37)
  - 1991 (DVD)., .81 cu. ft. (3 boxes) (Box 37 - 39)
    - 1991 Jan 10-11, 14-16, 17. (Box 37)
    - 1991 Jan 17, 18. (Box 37)
    - 1991 Jan 18, 21. (Box 37)
    - 1991 Jan 21, 22. (Box 37)
    - 1991 Jan 23, 24. (Box 37)
    - 1991 Jan 24, 25. (Box 37)
    - 1991 Jan 28. (Box 37)